in this video we're going to look at how
在本视频中，我们将探讨
to compute the mixed Nash equilibria of
计算的混合纳什均衡
a normal form game and in particular
普通形式的游戏，尤其是
we're going to go through the example of
我们将通过以下示例
battle of the sexes so what you've seen
两性之战，所以你所看到的
so far about equilibria kind of suggests
到目前为止关于均衡的建议
that it's really easy to come up with an
拿出一个
equilibrium but in fact as games get big
平衡，但实际上随着游戏变大
and general sometimes it can be pretty
一般情况下，有时会很漂亮
tricky to find the equilibria have a
很难找到平衡点
game and Nash's theorem is kind of a
博弈，纳什定理有点像
funny theorem because it tells us that
有趣的定理，因为它告诉我们
something exists but it doesn't tell us
有东西存在，但没有告诉我们
how to find it it just tells us that it
如何找到它只是告诉我们
has to be there it's a non constructive
必须在那里，这是非建设性的
argument so what I'm going to tell you
论据，所以我要告诉你
today is sort of a starting point to
今天是一个起点
finding an equilibrium which is enough
找到足够的平衡
that it works in small games and in fact
它适用于小型游戏，实际上
you can turn this into a general
你可以把它变成一般
algorithm but not necessarily the most
算法，但不一定是最
efficient or insightful way of finding
有效或有见地的发现方式
equilibria so what I want to tell you
均衡，所以我想告诉你
today is that it's easy to compute a
今天是很容易计算
Nash equilibrium if you can guess what
纳什均衡，如果你能猜出什么
the support of the equilibrium is so
平衡的支持是如此
recall what a support is support is the
回想一下，支持就是支持
set of pure strategies that receive
一套可以接受的纯策略
positive probability under the mixed
混合下的正概率
strategy of the play of the players so a
玩家的游戏策略
an equilibrium support is a set of
均衡支撑是一组
actions that occur with positive
积极行动
probability for example that might be
例如，可能是
the support of an equilibrium so for
平衡的支持
battle of the sexes let's guess that the
两性之战，让我们猜测
subs let's guess that the support of the
潜艇让我们猜测
equilibrium is all of the actions so
平衡是所有行动，所以
let's look and intuitively that if
让我们直观地看一下
there's going to be a mixed strategy
会有一个混合策略
equilibrium of this game that looks like
这个游戏的平衡看起来像
what it should be so let's guess that
应该是什么，让我们猜测
that's the support and then try to
那是支持，然后尝试
reason about what the Eagle Librium
关于鹰库的原因
would have to be given that support so
必须给予支持，所以
let's just introduce some notation to
让我们来介绍一些符号
make this work let's let player to play
做好这项工作，让玩家玩
B with probability P and F with
B的概率为P，F的概率为
probability one minus P now if player
如果玩家现在的概率是1减去P
one is going to best respond to this
一个人将对此做出最好的回应
mixed strategy whatever it is and be
混合策略无论是现在还是将来
playing a mixed strategy in response
采取混合策略以应对
then we can reason
那么我们可以推理
that player too must have set P and 1
该玩家也必须设置P和1
minus P in a way that makes player 1
减P，使玩家1
indifferent between his own actions B
对自己的行为漠不关心B
and F so this is an important point in
和F，所以这是
reasoning about how mixed strategies
关于混合策略的推理
work so I encourage you to stop the
工作，所以我鼓励您停止
video at this point and just think about
视频，然后考虑一下
why that would be true before I tell you
为什么在我告诉你之前那是真的
the answer so the reason why player 1
答案是玩家1的原因
needs to be in I don't have the answer
需要在我没有答案
on the slide I'll just tell you the
在幻灯片上，我只会告诉您
reason why player 1 needs to be
玩家1需要成为的原因
indifferent is that he's playing himself
淡漠的是他在玩自己
a mixed strategy which means some of the
混合策略，这意味着
time he's playing B and some of the time
他玩B的时间，有时
he's playing off right because these are
他打得很好，因为这些是
both in the support they both get played
都在他们俩的支持下
with nonzero probability and if this is
非零概率，如果这是
an equilibrium then this is the best
一个平衡，那么这是最好的
response that player 1 is playing well
玩家1玩得很好的回应
if player 1 can play B some of the time
如果玩家1有时可以玩B
and F some of the time and be playing a
和F有时会玩
best response
最佳回应
he must be indifferent between playing B
他玩B一定很冷漠
and F if he's not indifferent if let's
和F，如果我们对他不感兴趣，
say B is better then he could get even
说B更好，那么他甚至可以得到
more utility by reducing the amount of
通过减少用量来提高效用
probability he puts on F and increasing
他放F并增加的概率
the amount of probability he puts on B
他放在B上的概率
and in fact he could get the most
实际上，他可以得到最大的收益
utility by putting absolutely no utility
通过完全不使用实用程序
on F and just all of the utility on B so
在F上，而在B上只是所有效用
the only way that he would actually want
他真正想要的唯一方法
to play a mixed strategy is if it's just
玩混合策略只是
the same for him to play B and F so that
他玩B和F也一样
means that we can reason that player 2
表示我们可以推断出玩家2
has set his probabilities P and 1 minus
设置了他的概率P和1减
P in such a way that makes player 1
P使得玩家1
indifferent and the reason why we've
淡漠以及我们之所以
bothered to think about this is we can
懒得想这是我们可以
actually write that down in math so we
实际上把它写下来，所以我们
can say the utility for player 1 of
可以说该播放器1的实用程序
playing B and here I'm kind of abusing
玩B，我有点儿滥用
notation you should really understand
你应该真正理解的符号
this to mean the utility for player 1 is
这意味着播放器1的实用程序是
playing B given that player 1 plays P 1
给定玩家1玩P 1，则玩B
minus P is equal to the utility of
负P等于效用
player 1 for playing F again given the
给定F的玩家1再次玩F
player 2 plays P 1 minus P
玩家2玩P 1减P
so then we can we can simply expand this
这样我们就可以简单地扩展它
out um taking into account the actual
嗯，考虑到实际
payoffs of the game and learn something
游戏的收益并学到一些东西
useful so we can say if it's the case
很有用，所以我们可以说是这样
given the same probabilities P and 1
给定相同的概率P和1
minus P the player 1 is indifferent
负P表示玩家1无动于衷
between playing B and playing F then
在玩B和玩F之间
that means well when he plays B then he
这意味着当他演奏B时，他
gets 2 with probability P and he gets 0
以概率P获得2，而他获得0
with probability 1 minus B so that's
概率为1减去B，所以
what we have written down here and when
我们在这里写下的内容以及时间
he plays F he gets 0 with probability P
他打F他以P出现0
and 1 with probability 1 minus P and
和1的概率为1减去P，而
that's what we have written down here
这就是我们在这里写下的
and now we just have a simple equation
现在我们有一个简单的方程式
in one variable so if we rearrange it we
在一个变量中，所以如果我们重新排列它
end up concluding that the only way that
最终得出结论，
player 1 can be indifferent between play
玩家1可能在游戏之间无动于衷
and being at B and F is if P is equal to
而在B和F处是P是否等于
1/3 in the same way we can reason that
以相同的方式我们可以推断出1/3
if player 2 was randomizing which we had
如果玩家2正在随机化
just assumed that he was then player 1
只是假设他是当时的玩家1
must make him indifferent and why is
必须让他冷漠，为什么
player 1 willing to randomize because
玩家1愿意随机分组，因为
he's simultaneously being made
他同时被制造
indifferent by player 2 so so now let's
对玩家2漠不关心，所以现在让我们
say that player 1 plays B with
说玩家1玩B
probability Q and plays f with
概率Q和f
probability 1 minus Q so now we can just
概率1减去Q，所以我们现在可以
do the same thing as before where again
再做一次和以前一样的事情
you should understand this to me in Q 1
你应该在第一季对我理解
minus Q and likewise here and we can say
减去Q，同样在这里，我们可以说
we can just expand it out in the same
我们可以将其扩展到同一个
way so if player 2 plays B then he gets
这样，如果玩家2玩B，那么他得到
1 with probability Q and he gets 0 with
Q的概率为1，而他的概率为0
probability 1 minus Q and if he plays F
概率1减去Q，如果他玩F
he gets 0 with probability Q and 2 with
他的概率Q为0，而概率为2
probability 1 minus Q we now again have
1现在减去Q的概率
an equation in one variable and we can
一个变量中的方程，我们可以
rearrange it and find that Q is equal to
重新排列它，发现Q等于
1/3 and the important thing to notice
1/3和需要注意的重要事项
that happened here is that
这里发生的是
player one and player two were both
玩家一和玩家二
willing to randomize so we ended up
愿意随机化，所以我们最终
getting out numbers here that made sense
在这里找出有意义的数字
we ended up getting P's and Q's that
我们最终得到了P和Q
were probabilities they were between
是它们之间的概率
zero and one and that means it's
零和一，这意味着
actually possible to set them in such a
实际上可以将它们设置为
way that player one and player two
玩家一和玩家二的方式
actually would be indifferent if the
实际上，如果
payoffs were different we might have
我们可能会有不同的回报
gotten something out here like 13 and if
在这里得到了一些东西，例如13
Q is 13 it means that B would have to
Q是13，这意味着B必须
happen 13 times more often than a 4
发生次数是4次的13倍
player 1 to be indifferent and because
玩家1漠不关心，因为
that's not a probability what that would
那不是那种可能性
really be telling us is there's no way
真的是在告诉我们没有办法
of making the other player indifferent
使其他玩家变得冷漠
and that would tell us there can't be an
那会告诉我们不可能有一个
equilibrium with the support but what we
平衡与支持，但我们
got out was interprete Balazs a
下车是解释巴拉兹
probability and that means there is an
概率，这意味着有一个
equilibrium with this support because
在此支撑下保持平衡，因为
what we've seen is if player 1 plays
我们所看到的是如果玩家1玩
this way and player 2 plays this way
这样玩家2就会这样玩
then they each make each other in
然后他们彼此交往
different and if they both make each
不同，如果他们都使每个
other in different then they're both
其他都不同，那么他们都是
willing to play these mixed strategies
愿意玩这些混合策略
and so in the end this mixed strategy
最终，这种混合策略
profile is a Nash equilibrium and so
轮廓是纳什均衡，所以
what we've done then is to compute a
然后，我们要做的是计算一个
Nash equilibrium
纳什均衡
after having guessed to support which is
在猜测支持之后
what we set out to do so the last thing
我们打算这样做的最后一件事
I want to think about here is what does
我想想这是做什么的
it mean to play a mixed strategy turns
意思是打混合策略
out there are different interpretations
外面有不同的解释
and and now that you can really see kind
而且现在您可以真正看到
of the mechanics of what's going on
发生的事情的机理
inside a mixed strategy you sort of
在混合策略中
better ready to understand some of these
更好地了解其中一些
different interpretations so the first
不同的解释，所以第一个
and kind of most natural is is kind of
最自然的是
the one that is going on in the matching
匹配中正在进行的
pennies example and that is that you
便士的例子，那就是你
randomize to confuse your opponent so in
随机混淆对手
matching pennies we each want opposite
我们每个人都想相反的便士
things and the only way we can be in
事物和我们进入的唯一方式
equilibrium with each other is if you
彼此之间的平衡是
have some kind of uncertainty about what
对什么有某种不确定性
I'm going to do if you know for sure
如果您确定，我将做
that I'm playing heads you just know for
我只是在玩脑袋
sure what you're going to do and it's
确定你要做什么，这是
something that I don't like and so
我不喜欢的东西
there's no pure strategy in this game so
这个游戏没有纯粹的策略，所以
the only way that we can be in
我们可以进入的唯一方式
equilibrium is if we're both a bit
平衡就是如果我们都
confused about each other but that
彼此混淆，但那
doesn't really describe what just
并没有真正描述什么
happened in the matching penny I sort of
发生在类似的便士
the battle of the sexes example that we
性别之战的例子，我们
just played here the other player and I
我刚在这里玩过
kind of want to coordinate the situation
想要协调局势
where
哪里
we both end up in different places or
我们俩都在不同的地方
one of us goes to the football game and
我们其中之一去看足球比赛，
the other one of us goes to the ballet
我们另一个人去芭蕾舞
is kind of an unhappy thing for both of
对于两个人来说都是一件不快乐的事
us
我们
what we both prefer is that we're both
我们俩都喜欢的是
in the same place and the only kind of
在同一个地方，唯一的一种
strategic element of the game comes from
游戏的战略元素来自
the fact that we have different
我们有不同的事实
preferences about our most preferred
关于我们最喜欢的偏好
activity so in the mixed strategy
活动，因此在混合策略中
equilibrium here it's kind of an unhappy
平衡在这里有点不开心
thing because of course when we play
因为我们玩的时候当然
this two-thirds one-third equilibrium
这三分之二三分之一的均衡
that we just looked at in battle of the
我们只是在战斗中
sexes where we have two one zero zero
我们有两个一零零的性别
one two if we're mixing there's some
一两个如果我们要混合的话
possibility that we're actually going to
我们实际上要去的可能性
end up in these uncoordinated outcomes
最终导致这些不协调的结果
that neither of us likes that's just
我们俩都不喜欢那只是
sort of an unhappy thing about the fact
对事实有点不高兴
that we're playing a full support
我们正在全力支持
equilibrium but and so it can't be that
平衡，但事实并非如此
we're randomizing to deliberately
我们正在随机地故意
confuse each other instead we should
彼此混淆，我们应该
really understand this randomization as
真正理解这种随机化为
reflecting uncertainty so if I'm
反映不确定性，所以如果我
uncertain about the other person's
对对方的不确定
action then and then I best respond
然后再行动最好
given that uncertainty and I do that in
鉴于不确定性，我这样做
a way that leaves you kind of uncertain
一种让您不确定的方式
in a particular way we can also find
在某种程度上，我们还可以找到
ourselves in balance that's really the
我们自己处于平衡状态
way that I understand the stability of
我了解稳定性的方式
the equilibrium and battle of the sexes
两性的平衡与斗争
that if we make each other uncertain in
如果我们彼此不确定
a precise way we can find ourselves in
我们可以找到自己的精确方法
balance even though we would really like
平衡，即使我们真的很想
it better if we were just to end up in
如果我们只是最终进入
one of these pure equilibria there are
这些纯粹的平衡之一是
two other interpretations that I'll
我将另外两种解释
mention here just to be complete we can
提及这里只是为了完整，我们可以
also think of mixed strategies as a
也将混合策略视为
concise description of what would happen
简明扼要的描述
if really nobody randomizes but we just
如果真的没有人随机化，但我们只是
play the game repeatedly so you can
反复玩游戏，这样您就可以
think of a mixed strategy as the count
将混合策略视为计数
of the pure strategies that would occur
将会发生的纯策略
in the limit and you can see how that
在极限，你可以看到
might also describe what happens in the
可能还会描述发生在
battle of the sexes game where if we
两性游戏之战，如果我们
just sort of bouncing back and forth
只是来回弹跳
between the different strategies
不同策略之间
weighting ourselves in that two-thirds
在三分之二的体重
one-third kind of way we would be in
我们将要经历的三分之一
equilibrium and sometimes we would miss
平衡，有时我们会错过
coordinate the last interpretation is
协调最后的解释是
that mixed strategies describe a
混合策略描述了
population dynamics so if it's the case
人口动态，如果是这样
that we have whole populations of player
我们拥有全部玩家
ones and
一个和
populations of player twos and we sample
玩家人数的总数，我们进行抽样
players from the population each of them
人口众多的球员
has a deterministic strategy the mixed
有确定性的策略
strategy can be an interpretation of
策略可以解释为
those population proportions so if it's
这些人口比例，如果
the case that the one population has
一个人有的情况
two-thirds B's and one-third FS the
B的三分之二和FS的三分之一
other population has one-third B's and
其他人口有三分之一的B
two-thirds F's if we were sampling those
如果我们采样三分之二的F
populations those populations would be
这些人口将是
in equilibrium relative to each other so
相对于彼此处于平衡状态
that's another story we can tell that
这是另一个故事，我们可以说
explains what equilibrium might mean
解释平衡可能意味着什么
what it means to be playing a pure
演奏纯粹的音乐意味着什么
strategy a sort of mixed strategy and to
策略是一种混合策略，
be in equilibrium there and that
在那儿处于平衡状态
concludes our discussion of how to
结束了我们关于如何
compute mixed strategy equilibrium
计算混合策略均衡